(Stephen:)Happy birthday to you.
(Penny:)Thank you so much.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe you're...
(Stephen:)Happy birthday to you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you're singing.
Well, I'm sorry.
(Stephen:)Happy birthday, dear Sheldon.
LEONARD:
Uh, Professor Hawking,
(Leonard:)if you just give us
one second,
(Leonard:)we'll light the candles,
and we can all sing together.
(Stephen:)I was crushing it,
but all right.
(Penny:)Okay, while they get
the cake,
(Amy:)Sheldon,
I just want to say,
(Penny:)I hope you didn't think you were
gonna get through tonight
(Penny:)without a hug.
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)You know, I used to hate
these hugs.
(Sheldon:)Now they're just
extremely irritating.
(Leonard:)Ready when you are,
Professor Hawking.
(Stephen:)And a one, and a two...
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Sheldon ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
(Leonard:)...to you.
(cheering)
(Adam:)So, who's taking me home?